tmuscle.com 2015-06-18

# T-Nation

**  
Information about the Company and its Web Site**

This privacy policy covers Testosterone Publishing, LLC, a limited-liability company based in the USA ("Testosterone"), as well as any of the company's affiliates and web sites.

Testosterone's principal activity is the manufacturing, sales, and distribution of nutritional supplements.  

**Organization Name:**

| 

**Testosterone Publishing, LLC**  
  
---|---  
  
Address: 

| 

PO Box 60310   
  
City, Zip Code: 

| 

Colorado Springs, 80960-6310   
  
State: 

| 

Colorado   
  
Country: 

| 

USA   
  
Controller: 

| 

Brian Maslach   
  
Web Site(s): 

| 

www.t-nation.com   
www.testosterone.net  
www.1500t.com  
www.tmagnum.com  
www.musclewithattitude.com   

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

Testosterone affords its web site visitors the opportunity to access the company's home page and browse its web site without disclosing any personal data. 

**Automatic Information Collection**

The company's web site does not automatically log personal data, nor does it link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

It does not use "cookies" to store personal data, nor does it link non-personal information stored in such cookies with personal data about specific individuals. 

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

Testosterone collects any personal data that visitors may volunteer while using the company's web services. 

The company does not, however, collect information about its web visitors obtained from other sources, such as public records, and public or private organizations. 

If you wish to access a table outlining the types of personal data that Testosterone collects, and/or to learn the purposes for which this data is used, please click here 

Testosterone does not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than those outlined in this table. 

The company may wish to use the personal data of its visitors for new purposes; in this event, it does not provide its visitors with any prior opportunity to consent to such new purposes. 

**Children's Privacy**

Testosterone does not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

The company takes no specific steps to protect the privacy of those children who disclose such personal data. 

The company does not provide — either on its home page or at other sites at which it collects personal data — information concerning its personal data collection practices as these relate to children.

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

Testosterone does not disclose any of the personal data it collects to outside groups or organizations. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

Testosterone offers its web site visitors the option of using a secure transmission method to submit the following types of personal data: 

  * primary personal data (such as name and contact details) 
  * identifiers (such as credit card information and web site passwords) 

The company has implemented policies, rules, and technical measures designed to protect the personal data it collects from the following confidentiality and/or security breaches:

  * unauthorized access 
  * improper use or disclosure 
  * unauthorized modification 
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

All Testosterone employees and data processors — as well as any other persons who have access to and/or who are associated with the processing of personal data — are obliged to respect the confidentiality of such data. 

The company pledges that no personal data it collects will ever be disclosed to any state or federal institutions or authorities, unless doing so is expressly required by law or other governmental regulation. 

**Access to Your Personal Data**

You can employ any of the following methods to determine whether Testosterone is storing personal data about you: 

  * e-mail (service@t-nation.com) 
  * postal mail to the company's address (PO Box 60310, Colorado Springs, CO 80960-0310) 
  * the company's telephone number (1-719-473-5500) 

At your request, Testosterone will provide you with a readable copy of all your personal data that it is storing. The company normally forwards this copy to you (free of charge) within a week of its receipt of the request. Be prepared, of course, to provide proof of your identity.

You may challenge the validity of any data about you that Testosterone stores; and, when and where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  * erased
  * rectified or amended
  * completed

Testosterone reserves the right to refuse to provide its visitors with copies of their personal data stores, but the company will present sufficient explanations in such cases. You may challenge any such refusals by the company.

**Privacy Compliance**

No national laws or self-regulatory schemes govern our web site or organization. 

No global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes govern our web site or organization. 

**Privacy Support**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact the following:

**Name/Designation:**

| 

**Customer Service**  
  
---|---  
  
Address: 

| 

PO Box 60310, Colorado Springs, Colorado 80960-0310   
  
Phone Number: 

| 

719-473-5500   
  
Fax Number: 

| 

719-473-7700   
  
E-mail address: 

| 

service@t-nation.com   
  
Testosterone is not aware of any other means by which the concerns of its web site visitors can be adequately addressed. 

**Personal Data Collected and Uses of this Data**

**  
Primary Personal Data/Business Information**

**X** | Volunteered by each visitor  
Collected from public records or bodies  
Collected from private organizations   
---|---  
  
**Primary Personal Data**

| 

**Technical Administration of the Web Site**

| 

**Research & Development **

| 

**Customer Administration**

| 

**Marketing**

| 

**Trading in Personal Data**  
  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
**Name**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

**x**

| 

\-   
  
**Gender**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Address**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

**x**

| 

\-   
  
**E-mail Address**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

**x**

| 

\-   
  
**Phone/Fax Number**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

**x**

| 

\-   
  
**Business Information**

| 

**Technical Administration of the Web Site**

| 

**Research & Development **

| 

**Customer Administration**

| 

**Marketing**

| 

**Trading in Personal Data**  
  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
**Employer/Organization**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Job Title**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Address**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**E-mail Address**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Phone/Fax Number**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Other Personal Details and Profiling Data**

  | Volunteered by each visitor  
Collected from public records or bodies  
Collected from private organizations   
---|---  
** ** | 

**Technical Administration of the Web Site**

| 

**Research & Development **

| 

**Customer Administration**

| 

**Marketing**

| 

**Trading in Personal Data**  
  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
**Personal Details**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Physical Description**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Family Characteristics**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Education and Skills**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Lifestyle or Personal Tastes**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Financial Resources**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**  
Identifiers**

**X** | Volunteered by each visitor  
Collected from public records or bodies  
Collected from private organizations   
---|---  
** ** | 

**Technical Administration of the Web Site**

| 

**Research & Development **

| 

**Customer Administration**

| 

**Marketing**

| 

**Trading in Personal Data**  
  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
**On-line Identifiers**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Financial Identifiers**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

**x**

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Identifiers Assigned by Public Bodies**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Biometrics Identifiers**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**  
Specific Data**

  | Volunteered by each visitor  
Collected from public records or bodies  
Collected from private organizations   
---|---  
** ** | 

**Technical Administration of the Web Site**

| 

**Research & Development **

| 

**Customer Administration**

| 

**Marketing**

| 

**Trading in Personal Data**  
  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
**Racial or Ethnic Origin**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Political Opinions**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Religious or Philosophical Beliefs**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Trade Union Membership**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Health/Medical Data**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Sex Life**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
**Police/Justice Data Such as Civil/Criminal Actions Brought By or Against the Visitor**

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\- 

| 

\-   
  
Close Window
